<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rdf:RDF xmlns:rdf="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#"
         xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
   <rdf:Description>
      <dc:title>Memoir of Hendrick Zwaardecroon, Commandeur of Jaffnapatam (afterwards Governor-General of Nederlands India) 1697. For the guidance of the council of Jaffnapatam, during his absence at the coast of Malabar</dc:title>
      <dc:creator>Henricus Zwaardecroon (1667–1728)</dc:creator>
      <dc:creator>Sophia Pieters</dc:creator>
      <dc:publisher>Project Gutenberg, Urbana, Illinois, USA., 2012-08-25</dc:publisher>
      <dc:date>2012-08-25</dc:date>
      <dc:rights>This eBook is for the use of anyone anywhere at no cost and with almost no restrictions whatsoever. You may copy it, give it away or re-use it under the terms of the Project Gutenberg License included with this eBook or online at www.gutenberg.org.
This eBook is produced by the Online Distributed Proofreading Team at www.pgdp.net.
Scans for this work are available from the Internet Archive (copy 1, 2).
In the same series, the following titles have also been published:

Memoir left by Jacob Christiaan Pielat to his successor, Diederik van Domburg, 1734 / translated by Sophia Pieters; with an introduction and notes by the Government Archivist. 1905
    Memoir by Anthony Mooyaart, Commandeur of Jaffnapatam, for the information and guidance of his successor, Noel Anthony Lebeck, 1766. Translated by Sophia Pieters, Dutch translator. With an introd. and notes by the Govt. Archivist. 1910
    Memoir left by Gustaaf Willem Baron van Imhoff, Governor and Director of Ceylon, to his successor, Willem Maurits Bruynink, 1740 / translated by Sophia Pieters, Dutch translator; with an introd. and notes by the Govt. Archivist. 1911
    Memoir of Cornelis Joan Simons, Governor and Director of Ceylon, for his successor, Hendrick Becker, 1707. Translated by Sophia Anthonisz, Dutch translator. With an introd. and notes by the Govt. Archivist. 1914
</dc:rights>
      <dc:subject>Jaffna (Sri Lanka) -- History</dc:subject>
      <dc:description>Memoir of Hendrick Zwaardecroon, Commandeur of Jaffnapatam (afterwards Governor-General of Nederlands India) 1697. For the guidance of the council ot [sic] Jaffnapatam, during his absence at the coast of Malabar. Translated by Sophia Pieters, Dutch translator. With an introd. and notes by the Govt. Archivist. </dc:description>
      <dc:identifier>pg:40579</dc:identifier>
   </rdf:Description>
</rdf:RDF>
